{
    "Question": "Which statement is true about field update actions from workflow rules and approval processes? Choose 2 answers",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Field update with “re-evaluate workflow rules” selected can cause a recursive loop if the updated field is included in a workflow.",
        "B": "Field update are not available on currency field if the organization uses multi-currency.",
        "C": "Field updates to records based on workflow rules and approval processes do not trigger validation rules.",
        "D": "Field updates are tracked in the history related list of a record regardless of whether or not History tracking is set for those fields."
    },
    "Answers": ["A", "C"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{
    "Question": "Universal Containers would like to automatically assign a specific permission set to new users. How can this requirement be met? Choose 2 Answers",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Create an approval process on the User object to assign a permission set.",
        "B": "Create a flow on the user object to assign a permission set.",
        "C": "Create a lightning process on the user object to launch a flow.",
        "D": "Create a workflow rule on the User object to assign a permission set."
    },
    "Answers": ["B", "C"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{
    "Question": "At Universal Containers, the Account object has a Master-Detail relationship with an Invoice custom object. The App Builder would like to change to a lookup field, but is not able to do so. What could be causing this?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "The invoice must have at least one Master-Detail field for reporting.",
        "B": "The Account record includes Invoice roll-up summary fields.",
        "C": "The Invoice records have existing values in the Account.",
        "D": "The Account is included in the workflow on the Invoice object."
    },
    "Answers": ["B"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{
    "Question": "What is recommended to refresh a full sandbox?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "After UAT sign-off.",
        "B": "Whenever a new production used is added.",
        "C": "After a major production release.",
        "D": "Within 3 hours of when it is needed."
    },
    "Answers": ["C"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{
    "Question": "When an opportunity close date is delayed by more than 60 days, the manager and the VP sales must approve the change. How can this requirement be met? Choose 2 answers",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Build an approval process that requires unanminous approval from the manager and VP of sales.",
        "B": "Create a workflow rule that checks for close date less that 60 days and add an email alert.",
        "C": "Create a lightning process builder flow that submits the record for an approval process.",
        "D": "Build a validation rule that does not allow a user to save the opportunity record."
    },
    "Answers": ["A", "C"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{
    "Question": "What is the true statement in regards to converting a tabular, summary, or matrix report to a joined report? Choose 3 answers",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Joined report blocks are formatted as matrix reports.",
        "B": "Bucket fields are not supported in joined reports.",
        "C": "Cross filters are not supported in joined reports ",
        "D": "The rows to display filter is not supported in Joinded reports."
    },
    "Answers": ["B", "C", "D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{
    "Question": "An app builder wants to show groups as the last navigation menu item in the salesforce1 mobile app. however, the app builder is not able to select groups as one of the items on the drop-down menu. What could cause this?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Groups is showing up in the recent section and not in the navigation menu.",
        "B": "Groups is not included in the selected list for the navigation menu.",
        "C": "Groups is included in the smart search items but not on the navigation menu.",
        "D": "Groups can not be the last item in the navigation menu."
    },
    "Answers": ["C"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{
    "Question": "Universal Containers is setting up salesforce for the first time. management wants the sales and marketing teams to have different navigation names in the salesforce1 mobile app. Which option is available to an app builder to satisfy the requirement?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Create roles for sales and marketing and assign a custom homepage layout for each role.",
        "B": "Create sales and marketing profiles to ensure read access to different objects.",
        "C": "Create mobile navigation menus for both the sales and marketing profiles.",
        "D": "Create public groups for sales and marketing and create mobile navigation menus for each group."
    },
    "Answers": ["B"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{
    "Question": "Universal containers needs to flag leads with one or more business areas. They need to add a field to capture these to the lead records. There is no need to report on this field. What is the appropriate field type?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Radio Buttons( multi select) ",
        "B": "Picklist ",
        "C": "Text area ",
        "D": "Picklist (multi-select) "
    },
    "Answers": ["D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{
    "Question": "Which objects can be members of a campaign? Choose 2 answers",
    "Options": {
        "A": "contact",
        "B": "account",
        "C": "opportunity",
        "D": "lead"
    },
    "Answers": ["A", "D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{
    "Question": "Which statement is true about an external id field? Choose 2 answers",
    "Options": {
        "A": "The field must be unique since duplicates are not allowed within salesforce",
        "B": "The field can be unique based on case-sensitive or case-insensitive value", 
        "C": "The field must contain at least one number and at least one letter",
        "D": "The field contains unique records identifiers from a system outside of salesforce"
    },
    "Answers": ["A", "D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{
    "Question": "Which statement is true about converting a lead? Choose 3 answers",
    "Options": {
        "A": "The lead’s most recent campaign record is automatically applied to the “PRIMARY campaign source” field on the opportunity",
        "B": "Users can convert leads that are associated with an active approval process", 
        "C": "Administrators may choose whether to enforce validation rules & triggers",
        "D": "The system automatically maps standard lead fields to standard account, contact, and opportunity fields"
    },
    "Answers": ["A", "C", "D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{
    "Question": "Universal Containers has deployed custom tabs through change sets, without including the profiles, to production (enterprise edition). Which statement is true in regards to the visibility of custom tabs?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Custom tabs are exposed for all users.",
        "B": "Custom tabs are hidden for all users.", 
        "C": "Custom tabs are default off for all users",
        "D": "Custom tabs are default on for all users"
    },
    "Answers": ["B"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{
    "Question": "A sales manager would like to look at an account record and view charts of all of the related open opportunities. Closed/wonopportunities, and open cases. How many report charts can be added to the account page layout to meet this requirement?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Three",
        "B": "One", 
        "C": "Four",
        "D": "Two"
    },
    "Answers": ["D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{
    "Question": "What is a key consideration when using unmanaged packages? Choose 2 answers",
    "Options": {
        "A": "A namespace is not required to create an unmanaged package.",
        "B": "The person who created the unmanaged package can change or update installed component", 
        "C": "The person who created the unmanaged package has no control over the installed components",
        "D": "A namespace is required to create an unmanaged package."
    },
    "Answers": ["A", "C"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{
    "Question": "A custom field contains a feedback score which is on a scale of one to five. End users would like a visual indicator of one to five stars based on the number found in the feedback score custom field. How can this visual indicator be displayed?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Use a custom formula field",
        "B": "Use a custom image field.", 
        "C": "Use a custom number field.",
        "D": "Use a custom text field."
    },
    "Answers": ["A"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{
    "Question": "The organization-wide default for a custom object is set to private. The superior profile grants view access to the same object. A user with the superior profile is also listed as the manager on the user detail record for a subordinate. However, the superior still cannot view records owned by the subordinate. What is preventing the superior from viewing records owned by the subordinate? Choose 2 answers",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Organization-wide settings for the custom object grant access to other user with the same role",
        "B": "The superior requires permission set in order to view the subordinate’s records", 
        "C": "The superiors’ role is not above the subordinate’s role in the hierarchy.",
        "D": "Organization-wide settings for the custom object do not grant access using hierarchy"
    },
    "Answers": ["C", "D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{
    "Question": "Universal container needs to update a field on an account when an opportunity stage is changed to closed lost. What can be used to accomplish this requirement? Choose 2 answers",
    "Options": {
        "A": "lightning process builder",
        "B": "Approval process", 
        "C": "Assignment rule",
        "D": "workflow rule"
    },
    "Answers": ["A", "D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{
    "Question": "Universal Containers sales reps can modify fields on an opportunity until it is closed. Only the sales operation team can modify the post closed follow-up dates and post closed follow-up comments fields. How can these requirements be met?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Use record types with field sets and restrict editing fields using field-level security",
        "B": "Use field-level security on page layouts to restrict editing fields.", 
        "C": "Use multiple record types, page layouts and profiles.",
        "D": "Use field level security to mark fields as read only on the sales profile."
    },
    "Answers": ["B"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "The VP of account management at Universal Containers has requested that all contacts mailing postal codes match the associated accounts shipping postal code. How can this be enforced using validation rules?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Create a validation rule using the distance() function.",
        "B": "Create a validation rule using a compare operator.",
        "C": "Create a validation rule using the geolocation() function.",
        "D": "Create a validation rule using a not equal operator."
    },
    "Answers": ["D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "The app builder needs to change the data types of new custom fields. The app builder is not able to delete and recreate any of the fields, nor modify any apex code. Which data type change will require the app builder to perform the additional steps in order to retain existing functionalities?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Changing the data type of a field used in an apex class from number to text",
        "B": "Changing the data type of a field used in a report from a text to an encrypted field",
        "C": "Changing the data type of a field used as an external id from number to text",
        "D": "Changing the data type of a field used in lead conversion from number to text"
    },
    "Answers": ["C"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Universal Containers wants to streamline its data capture process by linking fields together. They wish to do this so that the available value on dependents fields are driven by value selected on controlling fields. Which consideration supports the stated requirements? Choose 3 ans",
    "Options": {
        "A": "The import wizard only allows value to be imported into a dependent picklist if they match the appropriate controlling field",
        "B": "Custom picklist field can be either controlling or dependent field",
        "C": "Multi select picklist can be dependent picklist but not controlling fields.",
        "D": "Checkbox fields can be controlling fields but not dependent fields."
    },
    "Answers": ["B", "C", "D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Which type of relationship can be defined with external objects? Choose 2 Ans",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Cross organizational look-up",
        "B": "External look-up",
        "C": "External master-detail",
        "D": "Indirect look-up"
    },
    "Answers": ["B", "D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Universal containers is importing 1000 records into Salesforce. They want to avoid any duplicate records from being created during the import. How can these requirements be met?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Include a column in the import file that has either record names, Salesforce IDs, or external IDs that can be used to match records",
        "B": "When importing the file, select the “Prevent Duplicates” option on the last step of the Import Wizard and import the file",
        "C": "After importing all of the custom objects, run a duplicate check report, export the record to a CSV File, and run a mas delete to purge any duplicates",
        "D": "After importing all of the custom objects, review all records created and manually merge or delete and duplicate record"
    },
    "Answers": ["A"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "The director of marketing has asked the app builder to create a formula field that tracks how many days have elapsed since a contact was sent a marketing communication. The director is only interested in whole units. Which function should be used to calculate the difference?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Datevalue()",
        "B": "Now()",
        "C": "Date()",
        "D": "Today()"
    },
    "Answers": ["D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "What is true statement regarding master – detail relationship? Choose 3 ans",
    "Options": {
        "A": "A master-detail relationship cannot be created if the custom object on the detail side already contains data",
        "B": "A master – detail relationship cannot be converted to a look-up relationship",
        "C": "Deleting a master record in a master detail relationship deletes all related detail records",
        "D": "Master-detail relationship can convert to a look –up relationship if no roll-up summary field exist on the master object"
    },
    "Answers": ["A", "C", "D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "A new custom object is being created with a private sharing setting. The business wants to share individual records with specific people or group of people on a case by case basis. what options does the business user have to manually share individual records? choose 3 ans",
    "Options": {
        "A": "public groups",
        "B": "permission sets",
        "C": "roles",
        "D": "users"
    },
    "Answers": ["A", "C", "D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "To synchronize account, orders, and shipments in real time, a developer has built a custom interface between an external and salesforce. prior to deployment, the developer needs to confirm that the interface can sustain the synching of thousands of records at a time. Which sandbox environment is recommended to complete performance and load testing?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "partial sandbox",
        "B": "full sandbox",
        "C": "developer sandbox",
        "D": "developer pro sandbox"
    },
    "Answers": ["B"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "A custom object has a public reads only sharing settings that does not grant access using hierarchies. a dynamic sharing rule provides write access to the object to the global marketing public group if the record is marked as global. a user creates a new record and marks it as global. Who will have write access to the record?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "The global marketing public group and anyone above the owner in the role hierarchy",
        "B": "The record owner and the global marketing public group.",
        "C": "The global marketing public group, the record owner, and anyone above the owner in the role heirarchy",
        "D": "The record owner and anyone above the owner in the role hierarchy."
    },
    "Answers": ["B"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "In order to delete opportunities, universal containers would like sales reps to submit request for approval from their sales manager. What can be used to meet these requirements?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "two step approval process",
        "B": "approval process with apex trigger",
        "C": "approval process with time depenedent workflow action",
        "D": "process builder with submit for approval action"
    },
    "Answers": ["D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Universal container manages internal projects by department using a custom object called projects. only employees in the project’s respective department should have view access to all of the department’s project records. if an employee changes job roles and moves to another department, the employee should no longer have access to the projects within their former department. How can these requirements be met, assuming the organization-wide default for projects is set to private? choose 2 ans",
    "Options": {
        "A": "create a criteria based sharing rule using the projects department that grants access to users by permission set",
        "B": "create a criteria based sharing rule using the projects department that grants access to users by roles",
        "C": "create a criteria-based sharing rule using the projects department that grants access to users by public groups",
        "D": "create a criteria based sharing rule using the projects department that grants access to users by profiles"
    },
    "Answers": ["B","C"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "An app builder has been asked to provide users a way to identify a contact’s “preferred contact method” directly on the contact record. users need to be able to identify whether a phone number or an email, is the contact’s preferred communication method. which field type will allow the app builder to accomplish this with the fewest fields possible?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "formula",
        "B": "checkboxes",
        "C": "picklist",
        "D": "email"
    },
    "Answers": ["C"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "WHAT IS A TRUE STATEMENT IN REGARDS TO CREATING CUSTOM REPORT TYPES?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "WHEN THE PRIMARY OBJECT IS A CUSTOM OBJECT AND IS DELETED, THEN THE REPORT TYPE AND ANY REPORTS CREATED FROM IT MUST BE DELETED MANUALLY",
        "B": "THE DETAIL OBJECT IN A MASTER- DETAIL RELATIONSHIP CANNOT BE ADDED AS A SECONDARY OBJECT ON A CUSTOM REPORT TYPE",
        "C": "ONCE A REPORT TYPE IS SAVED WITH A STANDARD OR CUSTOM PRIMARY OBJECT, THE PRIMARY OBJECT CANNOT BE CHANGED FOR THAT REPORT TYPE",
        "D": "ANY OBJECT CAN BE CHOSEN UNLESS THE OBJECT IS NO VISIBLE TO THE PERSON CREATING THE REPORT TYPE THROUGH SECURITY SETTINGS"
    },
    "Answers": ["C"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Universal Containers has a requirement that an Opportunity should have a field showing the value of its associated account’s billing state. This value should not change after the Opportunity has been created. What is the recommended solution to configure this automation behavior?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "FORMULA FIELD",
        "B": "WORKFLOW",
        "C": "ROLL-UP SUMMARY FIELD",
        "D": "APEX"
    },
    "Answers": ["B"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "At Universal Containers, multiple departments utilize the Case object for different purposes. Some users submit cases for IT and HR requests. Other users provide customer support 999with case records. How can an App Builder enable different users to see different fields, based on the case type?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Create different case record types for IT, HR and Customer Support. Assign different page layouts to each record type by profile",
        "B": "Create different case field sets for IT, HR and Customer Support. Assign different field sets by profile",
        "C": "Create different case record types for IT, HR and Customer Support. Assign different page layouts to each record type by role",
        "D": "Create different case field sets for IT, HR and Customer Support. Assign different field sets by role"
    },
    "Answers": ["A"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Universal Container is using assignment rules to distribute cases to regional teams. Which of the following are true: (choose 1):",
    "Options": {
        "A": "It is possible to have multiple active assignment rules",
        "B": "Cases may be assigned to public groups (if configured)",
        "C": "Cases may be assigned to queues (if configured)",
        "D": "A workflow field update can be used instead"
    },
    "Answers": ["C"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Universal Container installs an unmanaged package. Which of the following are true: (choose 2):",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Components of unmanaged packages can be edited",
        "B": "Unmanaged packages have a namespace prefix",
        "C": "Unmanaged packages don’t have a version number",
        "D": "Tests are executed during deployment"
    },
    "Answers": ["A","D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Universal Container wants to store an area code and wants to be able to search for it in searches. Which are possible fields to store the data (choose 2):",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Text",
        "B": "Phone",
        "C": "Email",
        "D": "Multi Pick-list"
    },
    "Answers": ["A","B"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "External lookup: Links a Child (Salesforce or External) object to a Parent External object Indirect lookup: Links a Child External Object to a Parent Salesforce object (std or custom) 7)Universal containers has a custom object that has a N:M relationship with opportunity-LineItem carrying price and amount information. In order to compute total amounts and total prices per Opportunity using Rollup summary fields, what field type will you use (choose one)",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Junction",
        "B": "Master-Detail",
        "C": "Lookup",
        "D": "Cross-object"
    },
    "Answers": ["B"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Object specific actions cannot be added. Visualforce need to be embedded into a Lightning page. Universal containers have a custom object “service” which has a lookup relationship to Account. Universal containers want to enhance Salesforce1 with an action that allows account managers to enter a new service to an Account while looking at the account. (Choose one):",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Enter an object specific action to Account and put it in the Account Layou",
        "B": "Enter an object specific action to Service and put it in the Account Layout",
        "C": "Enter an object specific action to Service and put it in the Service Layout",
        "D": "Enter an object specific action to Account and put it in the Service Layou"
    },
    "Answers": ["A"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Which components can be added to a lightning app on custom Object: (choose 3)",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Visualforce",
        "B": "Standard Lightning component",
        "C": "Custom lightning component",
        "D": "Global actions"
    },
    "Answers": ["B","C","D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Universal Containers wants to rollout new product bundles with several pricing options. Pricing options include product-price bundles, account specific pricing and more. Which product satisfies the needs? Choose 2",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Custom AppExchange-app for product-pricing",
        "B": "Workflow on Opportunity/Opportunity Product",
        "C": "Formula fields on Opportunity/Opportunity Product",
        "D": "Lightning process builder"
    },
    "Answers": ["A", "D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Person Accounts (choose two):",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Do use space in both account and contacts table",
        "B": "Have the same icon as Business accounts",
        "C": "Can only be merged with other person accounts",
        "D": "Are enabled by default"
    },
    "Answers": ["A", "C"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "You want to use an External Data Object Table from Heroku carrying Product Category information. The data need to be included in Salesforce and searchable. What do you have to do before you can use the connection (choose two):",
    "Options": {
        "A": "press “validate and sync”",
        "B": "Choose “include in Salesforce searches” option",
        "C": "Choose “include as index field”",
        "D": "URL / choose the URL"
    },
    "Answers": ["A", "B"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Which is true about social accounts?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "You can use social accounts data even when you are not logged into the social account",
        "B": "You need a personal social account in order to see social account data",
        "C": "You can use social accounts to import data into salesforce",
        "D": "Connection to social account is established thru a companywide “named principal"
    },
    "Answers": ["B"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Which values must be defined when creating a new opportunity stage? choose 3",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Amount.",
        "B": "Type.",
        "C": "Probability.",
        "D": "Forecast Category."
    },
    "Answers": ["B","C","D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Universal containers needs the ability to generate contract documents. all the data required for a contract resea… custom object. which is the recommended solution?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Create the HTML template for contracts and store it in the public folder.",
        "B": "Store a template in the static Resources and configure the action link template to use it",
        "C": "Select the install an appExchange products to meet the contract generation needs",
        "D": "Enable the contracts feature and create a custom contract template based on the standard template"
    },
    "Answers": ["A"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "what type of field can be used to filter a report chart that has been added to a page layout?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Standard field.",
        "B": "Matching ID field.",
        "C": "Formula field.",
        "D": "Name field."
    },
    "Answers": ["B"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "To synchronize Accounts, orders and shipments in real time a developer has built a custom interface external system and salesforce.prior to deployment, the developer needs to confirm that the interface syncing of thousands of records of records at a time. which sandbox environmnet is recommended to complete performance and load testing?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Developer sandbox.",
        "B": "Full sandbox.",
        "C": "Partial sandbox.",
        "D": "Developer pro sandbox."
    },
    "Answers": ["B"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "In order to delete opportunities, universal containers would like sales reps to submit requests for approval form their sales manager. what can be used to meet these requiremens?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Approval process with apex trigger.",
        "B": "Two step approval process.",
        "C": "Approval process with time dependent workflow action.",
        "D": "Process Builder with submit for approval action."
    },
    "Answers": ["D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "what salesforce functionality is ignored when processing field updates in workflow rules and approval processes? choose 3",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Decimal places and character limits.",
        "B": "Record type picklist value assignments .",
        "C": "Field level security.",
        "D": "Multiple currencies."
    },
    "Answers": ["B","C","D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "what is a section of the lightning App builder tool? choose 3",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Mobile card.",
        "B": "Canvas",
        "C": "Components",
        "D": "Selected publisher actions."
    },
    "Answers": ["B","C","D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "what option is available to an App Builder when defining an object- specific create record custom action? Choose 2",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Specifying the fields and layouts of the action.",
        "B": "Redirecting the end user to the detail page of the target object.",
        "C": "Pre- defining field values on the target object.",
        "D": "allowing the end user to choose the record type."
    },
    "Answers": ["A","B"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Universal Containers provides access to Salesforce for their sales, service and marketing teams. Management wants to ensure that when users log in, their home tab provides access to links and documentation that are specifically relevant to their job function. How can this requirement be met?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Create separate home page custom components and layouts; assign to users by role",
        "B": "Create separate home page custom components and layouts; assign to users by profile",
        "C": "Expose specific elements within a home page custom component determined by role",
        "D": "Expose specific elements within a home page custom components determined by profile"
    },
    "Answers": ["B"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "What type of field can be referenced by a Roll-up Summary field using SUM? Choose 3 answers.",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Formula",
        "B": "Currency",
        "C": "Number ",
        "D": "Percent"
    },
    "Answers": ["B","C","D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Universal Containers has created the custom objects Candidate and Interview in Salesforce to track candidates and interviews respectively. The company wants to track the total number of interviews a candidate has gone through on the candidate record without writing any code. How can app builder accomplish this requirements? Choose 2 answers",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Use a roll-up summary field on the candidate record to show the total number of interviews",
        "B": "Use a master-detail relationship between the Candidate and the Interview objects",
        "C": "Use a lookup relationship between the Candidate and Interview objects.",
        "D": "Use a formula field on the candidate record to show the total number of interviews"
    },
    "Answers": ["A","B"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "When configuring a record type, an App Builder can configure the available value of a picklist field for the page layout. Which opportunity standard field is available to be configured directly in the Opportunity record type? Choose 2 answers",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Forecast Category",
        "B": "Lead Source",
        "C": "Type ",
        "D": "Stage"
    },
    "Answers": ["B","C"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Which capability allows an app builder to grant object-level access? Choose 2 answers",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Assigning a user a Profile that allows Read access to an object.",
        "B": "Assigning a user a Public Group that allows for Read and Edit access to an object",
        "C": "Assigning a user a Permission Set that allows Read and Edit access to an object",
        "D": "Assigning a user a Role that allows Read access to an object."
    },
    "Answers": ["A","C"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Which chatter Group type should the App Builder recommend?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Member Group",
        "B": "Unlisted Group",
        "C": "Public Group",
        "D": "Private Group"
    },
    "Answers": ["B"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Universal Containers conduct evaluations of their sales reps using a custom object consisting of numerical scores and executive comments. The company wants to ensure that only the sales reps, and their manager’s executive can view the rep’s evaluation record but the reps should not be able to view the executive comment field on their review. How can these requirement be met?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Use a private sharing model granting record access using hierarchy; manage field access with record types and field-level security",
        "B": "Use a private sharing model granting record access using hierarchy; manage field access with field-level security",
        "C": "Use a private sharing model granting record access using custom setting; manage field access with page layouts and field level security",
        "D": "Use a private sharing model granting record access using custom setting; manage field access with record types and page layouts"
    },
    "Answers": ["B"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "What may occur if workflow rules are reevaluated after a field change by a field update?",
    "Options": {
        "A": "A recursive loop potentially results in exceeding organizational limits.",
        "B": "Cross-object workflow rules result in re-evaluation after field change.",
        "C": "Workflow rules trigger validation rules on field updates.",
        "D": "Workflow rules trigger more workflow rules to be re-evaluated."
    },
    "Answers": ["A","D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Which statement is true when defining a Create custom action for the Contact object? Choose 2 answers",
    "Options": {
        "A": "The create action can pre-define Contact field values.",
        "B": "The create action will ignore field requirements.",
        "C": "The create action allows a user to select a record type.",
        "D": "The create action will respect validation rules."
    },
    "Answers": ["A","D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "Sales representatives want to capture custom Feedback record details related to each Account. The sales reps want to accomplish this with minimal clicks on the Salesforce1 mobile application. What is the recommended solution to meet this requirement? Choose 2 answers.",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Create predefined values for most of the fields",
        "B": "Create a global action on Account",
        "C": "Create a feedback object as a parent of Account",
        "D": "Create an object-specific action on Account."
    },
    "Answers": ["A","D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "The customer service team at Universal containers uses a custom Project object to track their customer projects. An App builder needs to create a relationship between the project object and the related client Account record. A private sharing model is in place for both Accounts and projects. Which statement is true when creating an Account lookup field on the Project object? Choose 2 answers",
    "Options": {
        "A": "The account record can include roll-up summary field with data from the project record",
        "B": "Users can only delete Accounts if they have access to related projects records",
        "C": "The account lookup field on the project record can be made optional",
        "D": "Cross-object field updates between the Project and Account records are not supported"
    },
    "Answers": ["C","D"],
    "Reorder": true
},
{ 
    "Question": "The VP of Marketing wants to broadcast an email to 10,000 contacts in Salesforce on a regular basis, but realizes Salesforce’s mass email functionality has a limitation on the number of emails that can be sent each day.",
    "Options": {
        "A": "Develop Apex code and Visualforce pages to send the emails",
        "B": "Research and evaluate products available on AppExchange to send mass emails",
        "C": "Download all contacts to a CSV file and use an email client to send the mails",
        "D": "Request Salesforce increase the number of maximum daily mails"
    },
    "Answers": ["B"],
    "Reorder": true
},